http://drf.org/privacy-policy

PRIVACY POLICY
PRIVACY POLICY OF HEARING HEALTH FOUNDATIONHearing Health Foundation (the “Foundation”) is committed to protecting the privacy of its donors and constituents. The following Privacy Policy explains the ways in which we use information gathered from visitors to our Web site located at www.hearinghealthfoundation.org (“Web site”), as well as information provided voluntarily to the organization by donors, information seekers, and magazine and e-newsletter subscribers.  This Privacy Policy applies to all users of the Web site and all individuals and entities who provide information to the Foundation (collectively referred to herein as “you”).  If you would like to receive a copy of this Privacy Policy by mail, please contact our office.Information that Hearing Health Foundation CollectsIn general, anyone can visit our Web site and access published information while remaining anonymous and not revealing any personal information. Registration is not required to view anything on our Web site, including the current issue of Hearing Health magazine. We do not collect personal information from individuals via the Web site unless it is provided knowingly and voluntarily, as explained below. For security reasons, our web site collects IP addresses of visitors to our website, but this information is not shared with anyone outside of the Foundation and our web hosting providers.Hearing Health Foundation collects personal information knowingly and voluntarily provided by individuals through our Web site or to our office.  Reasons for voluntary submission of information include, but are not limited to, signing up to receive our Hearing Health Magazine, signing up for our E-Newsletter, submitting an online conference abstract for consideration, registering for an event, purchasing items online, donating online, by mail or by telephone, or requesting additional information.  The categories of personal information that we collect depend on the circumstances (e.g., signing up to receive our E-Newsletter versus donating online), but may include your name, address, telephone number, phone number, email address, date of birth, and credit card information.When Hearing Health Foundation Discloses the Information It CollectsWe will not disclose your personal information to third parties other than for the following reasons:you expressly authorize disclosure and/or it is necessary to complete a transaction that you have requested;disclosure is necessary or relevant to the operation of the Web site or the Foundation, such as in the case of sending Foundation mail or performing accounting or auditing services for the Foundation;the Foundation is required to disclose the information by law, court order, or other valid legal process, or to protect the Foundation’s rights or property; andthe information is disclosed to any successor organization to the Foundation or any acquirer of the Foundation’s principal assets.In addition, the Foundation does not trade, share, sell, or rent names of our donors or constituents with other organizations, nor send donor mailings on behalf of other organizations. Finally, when you send a donation in honor or in memory of someone and request that an acknowledgment be sent to another individual or a family, we will use the name and address of that individual or family for acknowledgment purposes only.How the Hearing Health Foundation Protects Your Personal InformationWe maintain commercially reasonable physical, electronic, and administrative safeguards to protect your personal information from unauthorized or inappropriate access.Additionally, access to confidential information is limited to those who open the mail and who process, steward and receipt donor contributions. HHF also uses encrypted data and a secure online donation portal. Web security is a priority of the Foundation and we work with our tech team to ensure information is protected as best as we can.Links to Other Web SitesOur Web site contains links to other non-Hearing Health Foundation web sites. Although we try to link only to Web sites that share our concern for customer information privacy, we are not responsible for the content, security or privacy practices of such third-party web sites. This Web site will, on occasion, use a secure third-party web site for event registration and abstract submissions. If you are not comfortable using a third-party web site to register for an event or submit an online abstract, please contact the Foundation’s office to make alternative arrangements. The Foundation uses Authorize.net to accept credit card donations. Those who wish to make a donation without using a credit card should contact our office to learn about other options.CookiesOther than the specific instances outlined in this Privacy Policy, the Foundation does not collect personal information about users or how individuals use the site. The Foundation also does not use the information-tracking devices made possible through "cookies," which are small pieces of data that may be sent to your Web browser from a server and stored on your computer's hard drive.How to Update Personal InformationYou may review, update or remove the information that you have provided to us through this Web site by contacting us. Moreover, you may always contact us to remove your personal information from our general mailing list, Hearing Health Magazine mailing list, or email list at any time.Changes to this Privacy PolicyWe may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time to reflect new or changed features and services, changes in the law, or changes in our use or collection of personal information.  We display an effective date on this Privacy Policy so you can tell when there has been a change.  If we make a change regarding our use or disclosure of personal information, we will provide notice of such change on the Web site. Your continued use of the Web site after notice of a new or revised Privacy Policy is posted on the Web site shall constitute your acceptance of any such changes to the Privacy Policy.NoticeOur Web site is not intended for or directed at persons under 13 years of age. We do not knowingly solicit or collect personal information from or about children, and, with the exception of our Safe and Sound prevention program, we do not knowingly market our products or services to children.  The Safe and Sound prevention program is intended to educate children and teens about unsafe listening levels, and content is intended to be viewed in concert with an adult, such as a parent or teacher.How to Contact UsShould you have other questions or concerns about the Privacy Policy, or if you would like to opt out of sharing your information with affiliated non-profit organizations, please contact us at:Hearing Health Foundation575 Eighth Ave #1201New York NY 10018(212) 257-6410 Voice(888) 435-6104 TTYinfo@hearinghealthfoundation.org
